当我放声高唱
if I sing about leeches
蚂蟥就会自行退散
maybe they'll go away, la la la
啦啦啦啦啦啦蚂蟥退散了
la la la la la la leeches!
快走掉啊  蚂蟥们
Get off me, leeches.
我刚看见布丽顺着大路一边叫一边跑我就知道你出事了
I just saw Bree running and screaming down the trail.
呃  我不明白你为何会这么想
Well, I can't imagine why you would think that.
我简直是好的不得了啊
I have never been better.
我被蚂蝗叮上了  妈  我腿上都是蚂蟥
I have leeches, mom. i've got the leeches.
哦  对  你确实腿上都是蚂蟥
Oh, yes, you have leeches.
但是  你很幸运
Well, lucky for you,
每个好妈妈都会随身携带信用卡
Every good mom keeps a credit card handy
来预防紧急情况
In case of an emergency.
呃
Ugh.
这是另一个喜爱信用卡的理由啊
Yet another reason to love credit cards.
当年的女性是不会有信用卡的
Pioneer women did not carry credit cards.
你被取消资格了
You are disqualified.
请交出你的软帽吧
Please surrender your bonnet.
哦  不  妈妈
Oh, no, mom!
你的软帽发型太可怕了
You have horrible bonnet-head.
她说的没错
Oh, she's not wrong.
你看起来跟头野牛似的
You look like a bison.
那么 丽芙
Well, liv,
你是鲁尼家最后一个还在坚持的了
You are the last Rooney standing.
我对你骄傲极了
I couldn't be prouder of you.
你是我们中把金搅子
You're our last chance
带回家的最后希望了
To bring home the golden butter churn.
我才不在乎什么破金搅子呢
I don't care about some stupid golden butter churn.
我只是想和我的妈妈多呆呆
I just wanted to spend time with my mom.
哦 谢谢了
Oh, thank you.
你口中的妈妈指的是我  对吧
You are talking about me, right?
我想我只是有点嫉妒
I guess I just got a little bit jealous
你和玛蒂的母女时刻罢了
With all of you and maddie's mother-daughter time,
我也想拥有一些
And I just wanted some for me.
顺带一提  我可从没玛蒂的腿上刮过蚂蟥
I never scraped leeches off of maddie's legs.
谢谢你照顾我
Thanks for taking care of me.
你才是个实打实的好妈妈
You are one butt bomb of mom.
我终于把这老娘的架子给夺回来了
Mama got her butt bomb back.
砰 搭好了
Boom! dropped.